<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Coca Cola Climate Ambassador</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_icon">Navigation Drawer Icon</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Navigation Drawer Icon</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Navigation Drawer Icon</string>
    <string name="menu_search">Search</string>
    <string name="for_suppliers">For Suppliers</string>
    <string name="title_activity_business_case_module">Business Case</string>
    <string name="title_activity_key_interventions_module">Key Interventions</string>
    <string name="title_activity_engaging_suppliers_module">Engaging Suppliers</string>
    <string name="title_activity_internal_training_overview">Internal Training</string>
    <string name="title_activity_supplier_overview">Supplier Overview</string>
    <string name="title_activity_supplier_guide">Supplier Guide</string>
    <string name="value_chain_title">IN ACTION: OPPORTUNITIES ALONG THE VALUE CHAIN</string>
    <string name="value_chain_description">This module reviews key strategic challenges and opportunities for carbon reduction in each of 5 areas of the value chain:
                                                    ingredients, packaging, manufacturing, distribution, and refrigeration. The materials provide a strategic framework and
                                                    then follow a case-based approach, discussing 2-3 good practices (case studies) in each area. This module demonstrates how
                                                    to broaden your GHG action by working with suppliers, vendors, and partners. The course activities focus on showing the relevance
                                                    to the Coca-Cola business. </string>
    <string name="download_instruction">VIEW AND DOWNLOAD COURSE MATERIAL HERE</string>
    <string name="case_study_title">Explore Case Studies by Area</string>
    <string name="supplier_title">Sustainable Quality Growth</string>
    <string name="supplier_overview_subtitle">Partnering to Reduce Carbon along Our Value Chain</string>
    <string name="supplier_description">The Coca-Cola Company and its bottling partners are committed to realizing a 25 percent reduction of the carbon emissions embedded
                                        in  the “drink in your hand” by the year 2020.  As part of that goal, we are striving to find innovative ways to partner with our
                                        suppliers and customers to reduce emissions across our value chain. Together, we can grow a more efficient and productive business
                                        that protects our profits and the planet. </string>

    <string name="goal_paragraph_one">Coca-Cola’s 2020 Climate Protection Goal expands our prior focus on manufacturing to cover our full end-to-end value chain, which includes
                                        ingredients, packaging, manufacturing, distribution and refrigeration and integrates with other aspects of our sustainability framework for
                                        the first time across our system.</string>
    <string name="goal_paragraph_two">Due to its link to our entire value chain, the climate goal will have far-reaching impact and can influence and affect the carbon reduction of
                                        our Company, our bottling partners and that of our suppliers with an estimated prevention of more than 20 million metric tons of CO2 by 2020
                                        (the equivalent of taking 3.8 million cars off the road for a year). To achieve this 25 percent reduction goal, we will work with our partners
                                        and suppliers throughout our value chain and continue to move forward the energy efficiency and climate protection work within our system.</string>
    <string name="goal_note">Note, we do not intend to reduce the carbon footprint of every product in our portfolio by 25 percent, but instead the goal represents a total reduction in aggregate
                              across our entire portfolio/business.</string>

    <string name="supplier_vision">Our 2020 vision is to achieve sustainable quality growth. As we strive to increase the productivity and profitability of our business, we are equally dedicated
                                    to protecting the environment, and one of the ways we’re working toward that commitment is by minimizing wasteful carbon emissions.</string>

    <string name="supplier_quote">\"Reducing wasteful emissions is the right thing to do for people and the planet: and it\'s also a smart business decision.\"</string>
    <string name="supplier_vision_extra">We know that meeting our carbon goal will result in a more successful and sustainable business – pushing us to operate more
                                        efficiently and catalyze joint product and business innovations.</string>
    <string name="how_to_meet_vision_title">How? From the Farm to the Refrigerator</string>
    <string name="how_to_paragraph">Coca-Cola expects its partners and suppliers to work with us to do better.  We are already working with industry leaders to identify and implement more efficient
                                    and smarter business practices across our full value chain – from ingredients, to packaging, to manufacturing, to distribution, to refrigeration.</string>

    <string name="Ingredients">Ingredients</string>
    <string name="Packaging">Packaging</string>
    <string name="Manufacturing">Manufacturing</string>
    <string name="Distribution">Distribution</string>
    <string name="Refrigeration">Refrigeration</string>

    <string name="ingredient_paragraph">Around the globe, Coca-Cola seeks to partner with suppliers, farmers, universities and nonprofits to find solutions for more sustainable ingredients. With our
                                        partners we will reduce fertilizer and water use, make operations more efficient, and find better sources of energy.</string>
    <string name="packaging_paragraph">With a leading vision in bettering its packaging, Coca-Cola has sought out suppliers to develop innovative packages that reduce material use, lower transportation
                                        costs, and are friendly to the environment.</string>
    <string name="manufacturing_paragraph">Coca-Cola partners with expert vendors and technology providers to deliver more efficient operations and to invest in renewable energies around the world.
                                            From better compressors in our facilities more focus on how to integrate renewable energy sources, we seek strong partnerships that lead us to smarter
                                                technologies.</string>
    <string name="distribution_paragraph">Coca-Cola works with our distributors and vendors to green our distribution channels.  The Coca-Cola system teamed up with our trucking suppliers to develop
                                            hybrid vehicles designed specifically for our needs, reducing our fuel use and our carbon.</string>
    <string name="refrigeration_paragraph">Coca-Cola collaborates with retailers across many countries to install energy management devices (EMDs) on beverage coolers. Our devices can reduce energy use
                                            by up to 35 percent by monitoring usage patterns and then adjusting lights and temperature to maximize efficiency.  By using EMDs, retailers save on energy
                                             costs; and together, we improve our business and protect the environment.</string>
    <string name="join_us">Join Us</string>
    <string name="join_paragraph">Join us as we work to reduce carbon across our supply chain. Together, we can build stronger businesses and a better tomorrow.</string>
    <string name="supplier_quote_two">\"Coca-Cola seeks to deepen our partnerships with suppliers and customers that demonstrate a strong commitment to innovation, social, and environmental responsibility,
                                        and business success.\"</string>

    <string name="course_material_title">VIEW AND DOWNLOAD COURSE MATERIAL HERE</string>
    <string name="case_studies">CASE STUDIES</string>
</resources>
